Seen, Gulag channel, go go go!
Today, I took a behind-the-scenes shot of the gym!
So, today, we called in to the Goods Family, who has always been a great help to us!
We called up Mr. Goods Family!
You've been here really often already, haven't you?
Yes, I do.
But today, I'd like to introduce you to some of the things we do.
I hope I can show you what we are doing for everyone!
Let's start the video!
And then we'll do the rules tour now.
a little bit...
Ha-ha-ha!
Oh no!
You've never done this before.
I'm a frog family!
Ha-ha-ha!
I'll do the frog family.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, I don't know.
Frog family.
This is a stretching pole.
This is a stretching pole... and this is a miniature to loosen up your muscles.
Yes, we have a lot of things.
For midriff.
Gloves.
By the way, Claire has her own glove.
Hey.
You got it for me, right?
Yay!
I have one too.
I want one. We all want one.
Mmm-hmm.
When I push it, I stand on the ring over there.
I show it off in front of everybody.
It's a little embarrassing.
This is how you get in.
Entering the ring
I wonder what the background music is.
Countdown.
Wrong.
Trainer is shown
One, two, four.
Four.
four
Four...
Oh, I didn't project it.
Oh, wait.
Well, it looks like this.
And this is the one
The last thing I want to measure.
I'm not getting in.
You know, it really does show everything.
Body fat, muscle mass.
And...
Right arm, left arm.
The right one has more.
I use that a lot.
Oh, there it is.
I can't do it.
I can't take it down.
It's about 4.5 kilometers. Be careful.
Mr. Crazy, are you okay?
I can do it.
You know, this is hard.
It's so tight.
Oh, my God.
Don't drop it.
That's it.
Clear. Do that one.
This is the one that Kia and I did together.
Think of this as a baby.
You have to strengthen your core so you don't drop it.
Here.
Tsunami.
This is really bad.
Water.
This is how you keep your balance.
loose.
So, stand up.
from here.
Three.
That's good, that's good, that's good, that's good.
Ten seconds.
That's not safe.
Can I try?
I've never done it before.Never done it before
Firm and heavy.
Wow.
This is still a crazy core workout.
Stand up.
He doesn't listen to me.
You're good.
How many sets of these do you do?
This one.
Not three sets.
Oh.
That's really hard.
I can blow on a balance ball.
I've been working on it lately.
I've been told I should get a bigger killer.
No, I have a small killer now.
It's just that the big one is easier.
Nice.
Put the ball down first.
There's a non-slip surface.
You do sit-ups with it.
Like this.
It's good, right?
What's with the balance ball?
It wobbles.
It's like you're putting your core on it or something.
Let's do it like this.
I'll do it like this.
Like this.
It's easier than normal. When you get up, it's like...
It's really tough.
And, you know, Claire and I do this a lot.
I'll do it.
Do you have any new products?
I like the black one best, and Claire's going to get the blue one.
And I'm most excited about red.
You're the one who chooses.
Wow, I feel like Yuzu did that.
Here, take this.
I know, it's great, but... you're like a doll princess now.
Everyone's a doll princess now
Her butt...
This is bad, right?
You should run.
You're supposed to put the load on yourself.
I've seen athletes do it.
They run really hard.
This is scary.
It looks so slippery.
I can see it!
Oh!
I put on the hill!
It's tougher on this one.
Amazing!
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
I'm doing it. I'm blowing.
They're gone!
Ah!
I feel like I'm in an animal forest.
This way, please. This way, please.
This is the secret area.
Can you hear the footsteps?
Can you hear them?
It's what Claire usually does.
This way, sir.
This is for beginners.
It's for beginners.
I recommend it.
Won't the gun fall out?
It's over there.
I think it's the end of the world if you hold it.
If you hold it, it's over.
Let's take it down to the bottom here.
It's going to hit the top, and then we'll move it up.
Yes, sir.
Like a trainer at the gym.
Does this work the pecs?
Yes, sir.
Very important.
And you, Yoo? Watching over you.
15 kilos.
Right.
But it's got a slipper on it. Yeah, that's right. It's easy.
Hey, Yoo-chan.Yu-chan
Yoo-chan, a watchdog team
You want to be a watchdog?
Yes, watch over them.
Is something going to fall out of the sky? It's okay. It's okay.
You're doing this?
Well, I guess I'll do the basics.
Oh, shit.
Oh, there it is.
This is bad.
What is it?
Here we go.
What's happening?
It's really heavy.
I don't know how to describe it.
I can't come up with a metaphor.
I can't find a metaphor.
Like your father?
I don't know.
Dad, you're out of line.
That's great.
Yu-zu!
I can make one yuzu.
I'll take one then.
Oh? What are you bringing?
Oh, that way.
This one's tight, too.
Isn't this one really tight?
I'll adjust the weights on this one, too.
Do it. Here.
On your feet.
It's heavy, isn't it? Here.
It's heavy!
You have to make sure this one doesn't clunk, too.
Doesn't it hurt your butt?
This one is a lot harder than you think.
And the other way around.
Let's do it!
No, I've only done it once.
It's cold.
How do you do it?
Looking in the mirror.
Oh, cool.
Triangular handle.
Tacking on the upper arm
Let's do this one.
Oh, wow.
I wish I was here.
I see what you mean.
This is what my cab always does.
My virgin cut pulldown.
I don't know where to cut it.
Cutting from the shoulder is cool.
You look like quite the trainer by the way you're dressed today.
Nice to meet you, sir.
I'll be wearing it.
You're going to let me?
Wow.
That's about right.
Oh, it's tight.
It's working.
Welcome, welcome.
Three sets of 10, please.
I'm in charge.
You're in charge?
Rotring Luthor.
Trousseau.
These are abs.
Wow!
That's harder than I thought it would be.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
Wow, I've never done that before.
This really works.
It's harder than it looks.
I wonder if I can get a neck braid.
Tougher than wiping?
Tighter.
It's like this.
Watch out for the frogification phenomenon from here.
This is his face.
Lately, his main competition.
Akarasu-kun.
I'm getting more and more interested in him.I was getting more and more curious.
I asked my friends.
I wonder if it's with or without.
Maybe it's more "with" and "without.
But I don't know.
Even if there's a chance...
I'm hoping.
Oh my god that's the spirit
I want to say
I never lie
It's a matter of time
Hesitating, lost
Always on my mind
I can't control
Can't get over that boy
I've never had this thought
For the first time
Oh yeah
Can't get over that boy
Tick tock tick tock
I can hear it
Alarm in my chest
More ticks
Oh my
Digging bone heartbeat
Everyone will hear it
Countdown in my heart
So there you have it, a behind-the-scenes look at the team.
We had a little fun in the second half of the show.
Normally, we train seriously.
We are working hard to perform well!
If you enjoyed this video, please give us a high rating and subscribe to our channel.
If you liked this video, please give me a high rating and subscribe to my channel!
Bye bye!
I can't fall in love with you yet
Prediction by Takuhon